A Guide to the Building a Better Virginia Foundation 2002 records, 2001-2002
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Building a Better Virginia Foundation 2002 records, 2001-2002
The Library of Virginia
40226
3.375 cu. ft. and 8 boxes
Building a Better Virginia Foundation 2002
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Donald J. Finley, Executive Director, Virginia Business Higher Education Council, 800 E. Leigh Street, Suite 105, Richmond, Virginia.
Historical Information
Building a Better Virginia Foundation 2002 worked to secure passage of general obligation bonds by Virginia voters in 2002. Bonds for education and parks passed, but efforts to pass bonds for transportation improvements in Hampton Roads and Northern Virginia failed.
Scope and Content
Records, 2001-2002, of the Building a Better Virginia Foundation 2002 consisting of advertisements, announcements, articles, booklets, brochures, clippings, correspondence, editorials, emails, endorsements, flyers, folders, itineraries, legislation, letters to the editor, lists, memorandums, news conferences, news releases, notebooks, notes, opinion pieces, posters, programs, reports, schedules, speeches, and other papers, cds, and video recordings detailing the efforts of the Foundation to secure the passage of general obligation bonds for education, parks, museums, and transportation by Virginia voters in 2002. Governor Mark Warner, Lieutenant Governor Tim Kaine, Attorney General Jerry Kilgore, U.S. Senator John Warner, as well as other public officials participated in the Foundation's efforts.
Contents List
- Building a Better Virginia Foundation 2002. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Building a Better Virginia Foundation 2002-Leadership, and Foundation 2002 campaign files. (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 2002 GOB Referendum Pre-Planning Meeting, State Council of Higher Education for Virginia. (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Papers on 1992 bond issue. (Box 1, Folder 4)
- General obligation bonds, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- North Carolina higher bond campaign, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Summary of campaign plan. (Box 1, Folder 7)
- General obligation bond papers. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Kickoff. (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Norfolk kickoff. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Northern Virginia kickoff. (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Richmond kickoff. (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Roanoke kickoff. (Box 2, Folder 4)
- General obligation bond--education. (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Education bond information. (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Education (legislation). (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Education--projects and committees. (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Education bond flyer. (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Parks. (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Parks campaign. (Box 2, Folder 11)
- General obligation bond (parks). (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Commonwealth of Virginia Parks and Natural Areas Bond Act of 2002. (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Hampton Roads Partnership: Transportation Challenges and Opportunities (report). (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, September-November 2002. (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Foundation phone list. (Box 2, Folder 16)
- John Warner itinerary, 22 October 2002. (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Biographies. (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Endorsements--Fraternal Order of Police news conference, 16 September 2002. (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Endorsements--Virginia Hospital and Healthcare Association. (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Endorsements--governing bodies. (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Endorsements--education (boards, schools, organizations). (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Endorsements--chambers of commerce. (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Endorsements--private organizations. (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Endorsements--correspondence, papers, December 2001-September 2002. (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Endorsements--correspondence, papers, October-November 2002. (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Blue Ridge Community College. (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Central Virginia Community College. (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Christopher Newport University. (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Danville Community College. (Box 3, Folder 9)
- George Mason University. (Box 3, Folder 10)
- J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College. (Box 3, Folder 11)
- John Tyler Community College. (Box 3, Folder 12)
- John Tyler Community College. (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Longwood University. (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Lord Fairfax Community College. (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Mary Washington College (University of Mary Washington). (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Mountain Empire Community College. (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Norfolk State University. (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Northern Virginia Community College. (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Old Dominion University. (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Patrick Henry Community College. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Paul D. Camp Community College. (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Piedmont Virginia Community College. (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Radford University. (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Rappahannock Community College. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Southside Virginia Community College. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Southwest Virginia Community College. (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Thomas Nelson Community College. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Tidewater Community College. (Box 4, Folder 10)
- University of Virginia. (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Virginia Highlands Community College. (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Virginia Military Institute. (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Virginia State University. (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Virginia Tech. (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Virginia Western Community College. (Box 4, Folder 16)
- College of William and Mary. (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Community college checklist. (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Organization groups (anti-bond). (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Legal guidelines. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Media advisories. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- News releases. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Direct mail. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Newspaper ads. (Box 5, Folder 5)
- T.V. (Box 5, Folder 6)
- GoT.V. (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Video. (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Radio. (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Bond clippings, May, July-August 2002. (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Bond clippings, 4-15 September 2002. (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Bond clippings, 16-30 September 2002. (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Bond clippings, 1-19 October 2002. (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Bond clippings, 20-31 October 2002. (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Bond clippings, November 2002. (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Editorials, pro, July-August 2002. (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Editorial, pro, September 2002. (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Editorials, pro, October 2002. (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Editorials, pro, November 2002. (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Opinions, pro, 2002. (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Letters to the editor, pro, September-November 2002. (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Editorials, con, October-November 2002. (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Opinions, con, October 2002. (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Letters to the editor, con, August-November 2002. (Box 6, Folder 10)
- General registrars directory. (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Voting. (Box 6, Folder 12)
- 1992 election results. (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Voter turnout, November 2001. (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Early information kit. (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Sample event kit. (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous papers. (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Brochures, bumper stickers, stationery, folders, and related papers. (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Banners, posters. (Box 7, Folder 2)
- T-shirt. (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Video tapes of commercials, focus groups, interviews, and other programming. (Box 8)